<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>2014/2015 Away Days &#8211; Cornwall Trip</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cornwalltrip.github.io/archives/category/runaway-days/20142015-away-days/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cornwalltrip.github.io/</link>
	<description>Annual golfing pilgrimage</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 19:28:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Summer Away Day &#8211; July 19th, 2015</title>
		<link>https://cornwalltrip.github.io/archives/370</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2014/2015 Away Days]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.cornwalltrip.uk/?p=370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[South Cerney Golf Club Once again Dave Mitchell hosted our summer away-day at South Cerney. Eleven of us enjoyed some warm sunshine and an aerial display from the International Air Tatoo at nearby Fairford. The team game was the dreaded &#8220;Yellow Ball&#8221; where competitors have the added stress of letting their team mates down rather [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>South Cerney Golf Club</h3>
<p>Once again Dave Mitchell hosted our summer away-day at South Cerney. Eleven of us enjoyed some warm sunshine and an aerial display from the International Air Tatoo at nearby Fairford.</p>
<p>The team game was the dreaded &#8220;Yellow Ball&#8221; where competitors have the added stress of letting their team mates down rather than just themselves.</p>
<p>The team prize was won by Sue, Geoff, Reg and our host &#8211; Dave M with a score of 105 points. Worthy winners as they were the only team to return the Yellow ball safely.</p>
<p>Individual winner on the day was Sue with 37 points. Christine was runner up with the same score but a paltry 19 points on the back nine!</p>
<p>Sue also secured a birdie 2 on the long Par 3 6th hole. This feat was made more remarkable by the flypast of Spitfires and Hurricanes that accompanied it.</p>
<p>We all look forward to the next away day at Chipping Norton. See <a href="http://www.cornwalltrip.uk/?p=372">here</a> for more details.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Away Day &#8211; Sunday, 19th April, 2015</title>
		<link>https://cornwalltrip.github.io/archives/38</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 13:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2014/2015 Away Days]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.cornwalltrip.uk/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[West Berks Golf Club A select band of eight players attended the day at West Berks. The team event was won by messrs D Scott, G Scott, R Edmonds and R Brown with a score of 87 points easily vanquishing their opponents Harris, Gent, Sykes and Sue Scott, who did have the honour of a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>West Berks Golf Club</h3>
<p class="paragraph_style_5"><span class="style">A select band of eight players attended the day at West Berks.<br />
</span></p>
<p class="paragraph_style_5"><span class="style">The team event was won by messrs D Scott, G Scott, R Edmonds and R Brown with a score of 87 points easily vanquishing their opponents Harris, Gent, Sykes and Sue Scott, who did have the honour of a team member John Gent making a birdie at the 11th.<br />
</span></p>
<p class="paragraph_style_2">Reg Brown prevented Dave clearing up on the spot prizes by taking the newly introduced nearest-the-pin-in-3 on the 13th, otherwise, the nearest-the-pin-in-2 on the 3rd, nearest-the-pin on the 7th and longest-drive on the last were Dave’s!</p>
<p class="paragraph_style_2">In the individual event, Dave and Richard both started well with 19 and 21 points on the outward 9, but challenges coming home saw them each record 33 points with Dave edging into 2nd place on countback.</p>
<p class="paragraph_style_2">The winning score of 36 points was recorded by Peter Harris out in 20 and back in 16. Can this form last for a month until the main event in Cornwall? Only time will tell&#8230;..</p>
<h4 class="paragraph_style_2">Individual Event</h4>
<ol>
<li>Peter Harris &#8211; 36 pts</li>
<li>Dave Scott &#8211; 33 pts</li>
<li>Richard Edmonds &#8211; 33 pts</li>
</ol>
<h4>Team Event</h4>
<ol>
<li>Dave, Geoff, Reg, Richard &#8211; 87 pts</li>
<li>Peter, Martin, Sue, John &#8211; less pts</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
